<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Matchezy</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_screen">HomeScreen</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="err_msg_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Enter valid email address</string>
    <string name="err_msg_password">Enter the password</string>
    <string name="err_msg_number">Enter the number</string>
    <string name="err_msg_dateofbirth">Enter the date of birth</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="facebook_app_id">2050448775215357</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb2050448775215357</string>
    <string name="google_places_api_key">AIzaSyC8K65LmB5kRjdksN_Frib3rm90_z28964</string>
    <string name="matchezy">Matchezy</string>
    <string name="title_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="biotext">
        Why read motivational sayings? For motivation! You might need a bit, if you can use last year’s list of goals this year because it’s as good as new. All of us can benefit from inspirational thoughts. \n\n
        “Be more concerned with your character than with your reputation. Your character is what you really are while your reputation is merely what others think you are.” \n – Dale Carnegie  \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="about_us">


       Some of us have it. Some of us seek it.\n
      It\'s this magical thing that does inexplicable things to us. Some describe it as a tingly sensation, some say it’s like millions of butterflies that flutters in the stomach, some say its spreading wings and flying high. To some its what completes them and gives meaning to their life. History is filled with it. There are many movies and books about it; Innumerable number of poems and songs about it. We all have heard stories as we grew up and earned it. We at matchezy believe it’s the most important thing in life.
\n\n
        I wonder, by my troth, what thou and I \n
        Did, till we loved? Were we not weaned till then? \n
        But sucked on country pleasures, childishly? \n
        Or snorted we in the Seven Sleepers\’ den? \n
        \’Twas so; but this, all pleasures fancies be \n
      \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t- John Donne\n\n

      We know it by many names Love, Kadhal, Amour, Pyaar. Some find love in classrooms, some find love in work place, to some love just happens out of the blue. Matches maybe made in heaven but we would like to play cupid and give you a place to find your love, your other half, your soulmate.\n
      We believe a perfect match should have the right mix of chemistry and compatibility. We showcase matches to you based on interest. Do you Love Pets? find someone who loves them too; Love books? find a bibliophile; Love rains ? find a pluviophile; Love Wine ? find a oneophile. Are you an activist, a vegan, an environmentalist ? Find someone just like you. The number of interest you could add is not limited, we believe every individual is unique.\n\n

      Love is blind, but you don\'t have to be. Go through the profiles leisurely. Learn their likes and dislikes, their qualification, learn who they are. Don\'t be hasty, you don\'t have to swipe, the profiles aren\’t going anywhere, just bookmark the profiles you like the best. Come back later and decide to express your interest. If you express interest, we notify them and if they like you back you both can start chatting. Like them ? Go on, meet them, get to know them better.\n\n

      Matchezy is completely free. We believe love transcends religion, language and geography and hence we give you complete freedom to explore. \n\n

      Write to us at support@matchezy.com to give us your love. \n\n

      Wish you all the best in finding Love ! \n\n

      Love, \n Matchezy \n

    </string>


    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><![CDATA[

    <h3>Welcome to Matchezy!</h3>
<p>PLEASE READ TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY. BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, ACCESSING OR USING ANY MATCHEZY APPLICATIONS. \n\n </p>
<p>YOU AGREE TO SUCH MATCHEZY APPLICATIONS SOLELY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT (THE "AGREEMENT"), AND YOU AGREE THAT YOU ARE BOUND BY AND ARE A PARTY TO THIS AGREEMENT. YOU WARRANT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST EIGHTEEN YEARS OLD AND THAT YOU HAVE THE LEGAL CAPACITY TO ENTER INTO CONTRACTS. YOU WARRANT THAT YOU ARE NOT A CITIZEN OF ANY COUNTRY THAT IS PART OF THE EU. \n\n</p>
<p>YOUR USE OF THE MATCHEZY APPLICATIONS IS EXPRESSLY CONDITIONED ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, YOU MAY NOT DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, ACCESS OR USE THE MATCHEZY APPLICATIONS. \n\n</p>
<p>As an Einheit Online Pvt Ltd. ("Matchezy" or "Matchezy.co") member or a beneficiary of Matchezy services, you are obliged to conform to the Matchezy terms of use given below. Please go through them carefully. If you object to anything in the Matchezy terms of use or the Matchezy privacy policy, please do not use the website or app or the service. \n\n</p>
<p>Matchezy is an online community where members can advertise their profiles for finding potential life partners. Members can view the public details of other members and invite them to connect. If the invitation is accepted, these members get connected and they will be able to message each other using the Matchezy messaging feature. Connected members may have access to each other\'s private contact details such as email id and phone number. \n\n</p>
<p>Matchezy is a closed community and its members are chosen with utmost care to ensure that members get to meet the very best. Matchezy does not owe any explanation to the applicants whose applications are rejected without notice. Matchezy can choose to, or choose not to approve an applicant without any explanation. Matchezy will not be able to stand guarantee about the identity or the character of its members. Matchezy may delete any approved applications at any point without notice and without explanation. Matchezy also does not guarantee a match or a response from any user. \n\n</p>
<p>Membership to Matchezy is free. Upon apply for Matchezy membership, Matchezy reserves the right to initiate communication with the person through voice chat, audio chat, email, phone or any means of communication superseding any preferences set by you or registration done with Do Not Disturb (DND Register) or National Customer Preference Register (NCPR) policy. You agree to Matchezy using emails, SMS and other means to notify and engage you with the service. \n\n </p>

<p>Matchezy members are expected to conduct themselves with a high level of dignity and professionalism. Unacceptable behaviour can lead to termination of their membership or even other legal action. The below etiquette is expected of Matchezy users and members : \n\n </p>
<ul type="disc">
<li>\t You will not post, or transmit to other members, any defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, obscene, profane, offensive, sexually oriented, threatening, harassing, racially offensive, or illegal material, or any material that infringes or violates another party\'s rights.</li>
<li>\t You will not provide inaccurate, misleading or false information to Matchezy or to any other member.</li>
<li>\t You will not use the Matchezy website or app for soliciting your own business activities.</li>
<li>\t You will not use a robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or process to retrieve, index, "data mine", or in any way reproduce or bypass the navigational structure or presentation of the Service or its contents.</li>
<li>\t You will not publish links to other websites.</li>
<li>\t You are not permitted to share details of Matchezy login with another person.</li>
<li>\t You should be using your discretion while sharing personal information with other members on Matchezy. Matchezy Members are expected to exercise simple precautions for their privacy and safety.</li>
<li>\t You will not post content that is vulgar, defamatory, controversial, violative of copyrights and trademark rights, violative of any law that the publishing of such content may be subject to.</li>
<li>\t You will use in a lawful, responsible and respectful manner, any information provided by another Matchezy member.</li>
<li>\t You will not share/solicit personally identifiable information or use derogatory language in the written spaces on Matchezy, including on \'My Story\', \'Date Plan\' and any other sections or features that may be included in the future.</li>
</ul>
<p>\n\nMatchezy reserves the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that Matchezy shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the service.\n\n
Matchezy provides assistance and guidance through its customer care team. When communicating with us, you agree to not be abusive, obscene, profane, offensive, sexist, threatening, harassing, racially offensive, or indulge in any other inappropriate behaviour. If we feel that your behavior towards our customer care team or any other employee is threatening or offensive, we reserve the right to immediately terminate your account without any warning. \n\n</p>


<h3>Eligibility</h3>
<p>You are eligible for a membership on Matchezy if you are at least 18 years of age and if you are not a citizen of any country that is a part of the EU.\n\n</p>


<h3>Content</h3>
<p>Matchezy owns and retains all proprietary rights in the website or app or the service. The website may contain copyrighted material, trademarks, and other proprietary information of Matchezy, and its licensors. Except for that information which is in the public domain or for which you have been given written permission, you may not copy, modify, publish, transmit, distribute, perform, display, or sell any such proprietary information. We also reserve our right to take legal action (civil and/or criminal) wherever applicable for any violations. In order to protect Matchezy and/or our members from any abuse, Matchezy reserves the right to take appropriate steps, using its sole discretion. \n\n</p>
<p>Matchezy reserves the right to modify, delete any content posted by the members on Matchezy, which in the sole judgement of Matchezy does not conform to this agreement or which might be offensive, illegal, or that might violate the rights, harm, or threaten the safety of either Matchezy and/or its Members. Matchezy reserves the right to terminate your membership, to suspend a profile or to disable access in respect of any member in breach of any of the terms with or without notice. \n\n</p>
<p>With respect to the content provided by you, that will be viewable by all Matchezy members, you hereby unconditionally and irrevocably grant to Matchezy the license to use, distribute, reproduce, modify, and publicly display such content on the website or app and to Matchezy members from time to time. \n\n</p>
<p>You agree that the sole purpose of using Matchezy services would be to connect with other Matchezy members to date and evaluate them for companionship(Marriage or live in as directed by law). You are prohibited from using Matchezy services to promote or solicit any of your other business agendas. \n\n</p>
<p>Matchezy does not (i) guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information on the service, or (ii) adopt, endorse or accept responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice, or statement made by any party that appears on the website or app. Under no circumstances will Matchezy or its affiliates be responsible for any loss or damage resulting from your reliance on information or other content posted on the Website or transmitted to or by any members. \n\n</p>
<p>All information that you include in your profile on Matchezy must be accurate, complete and pertinent. \n\n</p>


<h3>Privacy</h3>
<p>The use of Matchezy is governed by Matchezy\'s privacy policy. \n\n</p>

<h3>Disputes</h3>
<p>You are solely responsible for your interactions with other Matchezy members. Matchezy reserves the right to, but is not obliged to, monitor the resolution of any disputes arising between Matchezy members. Matchezy also reserves the right to take action, as deemed appropriate against errant members. \n\n</p>
<p>In no event shall Matchezy be liable for any damages whatsoever, whether direct, indirect, general, special, compensatory, consequential, and/or incidental, arising out of or relating to the conduct of you or anyone else in connection with the use of the service, including without limitation, bodily injury, emotional distress, and/or any other damages resulting from communications or meetings with other registered users of this service or persons you meet through this service. You agree to take reasonable precautions in all interactions with other members of the service, particularly if you decide to meet offline or in person. You understand that Matchezy makes no guarantees, either expressed or implied, regarding your ultimate compatibility with individuals you meet through the service. You should not provide your financial information (for example, your credit card or bank account information) to other members. \n\n</p>
<p>These terms of use shall be governed in all respects by the laws of India and you agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Chennai, Tamil Nadu. \n\n</p>


<h3>Copyright</h3>
<p>You may not post, distribute, or reproduce in any way any copyrighted material, trademarks, or other proprietary information without obtaining the prior written consent of the owner of such proprietary rights. Without limiting the foregoing, if you believe that your work has been copied and posted on the Service in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide our copyright agent (<a href="mailto:support@matchezy.com">support@matchezy.com</a>) with the following information:\n\n</p>
<ul type="disc">
<li>\t An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest</li>
<li>\t A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed</li>
<li>\t A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Website</li>
<li>\t Your address, telephone number, and email address</li>
<li>\t A written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law</li>
<li>\t A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner\'s behalf.</li>
</ul>


<h3>External Links</h3>
<p>The service may provide, or third parties may provide, links to other world wide web sites or resources. Because Matchezy has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that Matchezy is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that Matchezy shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of, or reliance upon, any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource. Please go through the terms and privacy policies of such sites carefully as you would be bound by those during such interactions. \n\n </p>
<p>We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to the terms of use and privacy policy at any time. The most updated version is available on our app and website at all times along with the date of last revision. Please check the terms of use and privacy policy periodically for changes as all modifications are effective upon publication. Continued use of the Matchezy app and website after revision indicates the user\'s acceptance of the terms of use. </p>


	]]></string>


    <string name="privacy_policy"><![CDATA[

    <p>Matchezy is strongly committed to your right to privacy. This section covers Matchezy\'s privacy statement that highlights how we handle personally identifiable information that Matchezy collects when you are on our website or app. Please read this privacy policy carefully. All information covered by Matchezy\'s privacy policy will continue to be protected under Matchezy\'s privacy policy irrespective of the outcome of your membership application or any change in your membership status in the future. \n\n </p>


<h3>How do we collect information?</h3>
<p>You directly provide us with most of the information we collect. You do this by filling out the registration details on the website or app, and by posting and sharing additional information voluntarily. We also collect technical information indirectly and automatically through our systems. This information may include logging your Internet Protocol (IP) address, software configuration, operating system and use of cookies; cookies are small files sent from us to your computer and sometimes back. Cookies ultimately help us improve your navigation and ease of use of our website or app. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information we collect about you</h3>
<p>Upon signing up on Matchezy with Facebook or Google, users authorize Matchezy to access certain information from these social networking platforms which is necessary to create their Matchezy profiles. We may collect information that can identify you such as your name, phone number and email address (\'personal information\') and other information that does not identify you. We may collect this information through a website or a mobile application. Information you provide such as name, email, mobile phone number and information we collect as you access and use our service either on the website or through a mobile device, including device information, location and network carrier may be disclosed to third party service providers who will help us personalize the app for you and perform behavioural analytics to create the most user friendly experience and to provide content according to your preferences. Any such information will be treated as confidential and private by such third party service providers and will not be utilized for any other purposes than which is authorized. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information you provide</h3>
<p>We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or our mobile application, or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, email address, mobile number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We may also use 3rd party APIs and other websites to validate the information you provide us. You also need to provide us information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown, location etc and these will be information viewable by all members. You have to fill in all mandatory fields on the application. If an applicant does not meet our criteria, their information will not be published on the website. If a Matchezy user deletes his/her profile, their information is discarded from the Matchezy website. Matchezy reserves the right to accept or remove any applicant or user without any explanation or notice. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information you post</h3>
<p>Upon acceptance of your membership, Matchezy gives you a profile based on the information you have provided. This profile is then uploaded onto the Matchezy Website/App. You can also post pictures, \'About\' yourself, and other information on Matchezy. You will be able to send messages to your connections on Matchezy via the Matchezy messaging system. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information from other sources</h3>
<p>We may obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from third party social platforms, such as Facebook and Google. When you access or use our website or mobile application through such a site, you allow us to access or collect information made available by the third party site in accordance with its privacy policy. This information may be available from your profile or account with such site or from cookies placed on your device by the third party platform. We may also collect information about you that is publicly available on the internet. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information from emails</h3>
<p>When you communicate with Matchezy, your email address and the contents of your email are stored with Matchezy to enable it to service your requirements. \n\n </p>


<h3>Information from cookies and other web technologies</h3>
<p>Matchezy uses cookies and other web technologies to maintain your session and customise your experience. Matchezy may use beacons or other web technologies to monitor usage of the Matchezy website or app as part of its on-going improvement of services. Matchezy may use third-party tools such as Google Analytics to collect general and non-specific information regarding usage patterns of the Matchezy services. \n\n </p>


<h3>We may disclose your personal information</h3>
<ul type="disc">
<li>\t in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;</li>
<li>\t to identify, contact or bring legal action against you if you are violating our terms of use or other rules or if we believe you are causing injury or interference with the rights of members, the general public or Matchezy;</li>
<li>\t if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us will be a part of the transferred assets; and</li>
<li>\t if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and other agreements or to protect our rights, property, or safety of our customers, or others.</li>
</ul>

<h3>How we use the information we collect</h3>
<p>Matchezy may use the personal information you provide in your application or interviews to verify your identity and gauge your suitability for Matchezy. In addition we may use the information you provide to  \n\n </p>
<ul type="disc">
<li>\t Deliver our product and services, and manage our business</li>
<li>\t Manage your account and provide you with customer support</li>
<li>\t Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others</li>
<li>\t Communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you</li>
<li>\t Develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites</li>
<li>\t Perform ad tracking and website or mobile application analytics</li>
</ul>
<p>Personal information such as name, email id and phone number may be viewable by the members you are connected to each other on Matchezy. No other members will have access to your personal information. Hence, by connecting with another member, you agree that you are willing to share such personal information with them. \n\n </p>
<p>We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this privacy policy. We process personal information on our servers in different jurisdictions worldwide. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. \n\n </p>
<p>Matchezy reserves the right to retain and store information or other data which is shared on it where Matchezy believes in its sole discretion that such information is vital to comply with the legal or regulatory obligations or for the detection or prevention of criminal or other unlawful activity or where Matchezy has a reason to do so, such as resolving disputes, enforcing our terms of use, to prevent fraud, for analytical purposes or for record-keeping integrity. If you delete your data from Matchezy, copies of your Matchezy profile may remain viewable in cached pages or might have been copied or stored by other users of our websites. All user information collected from Facebook or Google is permanently removed upon deletion of a profile from Matchezy. \n\n </p>


<h3>Third party websites</h3>
<p>If you leave the Matchezy Website and share information through any third-party website, such as Facebook or Google, then that information is not covered by this privacy policy and will be subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of the concerned third party websites. These third party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third party websites you visit by clicking on the \'privacy\' link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting. \n\n </p>


<h3>Security</h3>
<p>We take great care in maintaining the security of the website or app and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. \n\n </p>
<p>The company currently does not conduct any criminal and/or other formal background checks of all its users and also does not attempt to verify the statements of its users. \n\n </p>
<p>We review this privacy policy and terms of use regularly. Occasionally we may need to make changes or additions to this privacy policy and terms of use. We may post new versions of this privacy policy on our website. \n\n </p>
<p>We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to the terms of use and privacy policy at any time. The most updated version is available on our app and website at all times along with the date of last revision. Please check the terms of use and privacy policy periodically for changes as all modifications are effective upon publication. Continued use of the Matchezy app and website after revision indicates the user\'s acceptance of the terms of use and privacy policy. \n\n </p>

	]]></string>


    <string name="help_support"><![CDATA[

        <h3>Got a problem? \n\n</h3>
        <p>Contact us through our phone or email and let us know what we can do for you! \n\n</p>
        <p><b>Phone: </b> +919629499956 \n\n</p>
        <p><b>Email: </b> support@matchezy.com \n\n<p>

    ]]></string>

</resources>
